(Sheldon:)You're upset about Emily
and you're Indian.
(Sheldon:)I need to make you chai tea.
(Sheldon:)Now, I have all the ingredients
except cardamom seeds.
(Sheldon:)Do you happen to have any on you?
(Raj:)Sorry, I left them in my turban.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I'll make English breakfast tea.
(Sheldon:)They destroyed your culture.
That's close enough.
(Sheldon:)You know, I'm curious,
(Sheldon:)why are you so upset
about seeing Emily with another man?
(Raj:)Wouldn't you be upset if you saw
Amy out with someone else?
(Sheldon:)Can't happen. We have an ironclad
relationship agreement
(Sheldon:)which precludes her from physical
contact with anyone other than me.
(Raj:)But you don't have sex
with her either.
(Sheldon:)Slick, huh?
(Raj:)To be truthful,
Emily and I haven't dated that long,
(Raj:)and we never agreed
to be exclusive to each other.
(Sheldon:)Have you had intercourse?
(Raj:)No.
(Sheldon:)Well, stick to your guns.
There will be a lot of pressure.